seaked.com 2013-11-02

# Privacy Policy | Seaked

Privacy is very important to us at Seaked and we take responsible straps to ensure it remains important. The following Privacy Statement describes the types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Seaked and how these informations are used. We never sell your personal information to third parties and all information will be safe guarded. 

**Register An Account**   
In order to become a Seaked member, registration is a must on the site. To register for an account, you are required to provide a chosen username and password and your email address. We do not make your email address and password publicly available and we strongly discourage you from doing so. Once a member, you may provide additional publicly-available information in various areas of the Site, including the "Profile" area, chat rooms, message boards, comment areas, blogs and any other publicly accessible forum. This includes describing yourself, your opinions and your personal contact information. Providing this type of personal information is entirely optional, and because we are unable to control how others may use such personal information, you do so at your own risk. In order to share story information with people you personally know who are not Seaked members, you may enter their email addresses into our “tell a friend” or “email this” features. This information will be used by us to send a link directing them to this Site, including a message that you write. The email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation. If you participate in surveys, contests or promotions (participation is optional) we may collect certain additional information, including your name, company name, company address, telephone number, home address, email address, IP address, website from whence you came to the Site, travel preferences, favourite websites, family profile, age, whether you are a U.S. resident, employment profile, etc. 

**Email Communications**   
We will communicate with you through emails and notices posted on this Site. These include welcome emails, occasional newsletters, promotional information, daily site updates such as new content on the Site, and member communications to communicate important issues or changes about the site, or perhaps to notify members that there has been a comment on one of their articles, etc. Our emails may include the use of technologies such as single-pixel GIFs or other technologies to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails. You are automatically “opted-in” to receive our email communications and You may remove yourself from such services at any time. We have an unsubscribe link at the bottom of our newsletters, daily site updates and promotions. You may maintain your account with us and still “opt out” of receiving our newsletters, daily site updates and/or promotions. If you wish to unsubscribe from our member communications, however, you will need to close your account. See also the Choice/Opt-Out section below. If you ever have a problem with your account, please email us at contact@seaked.com. 

**Log Files (Clickstream)**   
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Once you leave the site, we do not track you. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites and tailor our Service to you. 

**Traffic and RSS Data**   
Like most other Internet sites, we track general site traffic data such as referring domains, browser type, time zone and other data. We also track statistics with respect to RSS, including number of subscribers, type of RSS aggregators, and other data. We use such data and statistics to administer the site, including managing comment spam, server loads, site design requirements, and other administrative purposes. We also use aggregated traffic data and statistics for marketing analysis, determining future offerings, and other business uses. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing London real estate ads to someone in London, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

**DoubleClick DART Cookies**   
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non-personally identifiable information.” It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/ You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

**Disclosure of Your Information**   
We may use your personal information to communicate with you regarding our Service, including providing information you have requested or products you have purchased. In addition, we may analyze and use your personal information - and supplement it with other information we obtain - to notify you and target advertising to you regarding special offers, products, services, and information that we think may be of interest to you, and to measure the effectiveness of advertisements on our Site. We may also use your personal information to do any of the following: (i) resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; (ii) respond to specific inquiries made by you; (iii) enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use; and (v) customize, measure, and improve our Services, content, and layout. We may disclose or report your personal information if we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary or appropriate to do any of the following: (i) comply with the law or with legal process (e.g., a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process); (ii) protect our rights or the rights of a third-party; (iii) ensure the safety of the public or any person; (iv) respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of others; and (v) prevent or stop potentially prohibited or illegal activities. 

**Third Party Service Providers**   
We engage certain trusted third-parties to perform various functions and provide services to us (for example, web hosting services and maintenance services). These third-parties may have access to some of your personal information, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third-parties to maintain the privacy and security of your personal information. 

**Privacy of Children**   
This Service is not available to children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18. If we become aware that a child under the age of 18 has provided us with personally identifiable information without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
You have the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out or change your user preferences via a link in the footer of most email messages. These options are also made available in the "Profile" area of your account. Alternatively, you may opt out by emailing us at contact@seaked.com. Some communications (e.g., member communications about important account notifications) are necessary for all Seaked members. You must close your Seaked account to unsubscribe from these communications. To close your BizSugar account, put “close my account” in the subject line and email us at contact@seaked.com. See also the Email Communications section above. 

**Notification of Changes**   
This Privacy Statement may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. If we change this Privacy Statement in any way that affects your privacy, we will post those changes on the Site. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. 

**Contact**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please email us at contact@seaked.com
